{"dsda":{"username":"dsda","assessmentData":[{"questions":[{"question":"I am only relaxed when I have total control over my life.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"Thinking about what Iâ€™ve done the past few months felt unenjoyable.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I often pretend to believe certain things so I can \"fit in.\"","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"When speaking to others, I generally don't talk about myself in a positive way.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I avoid talking about my culture because people might think it is weird.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I have stopped doing things I used to enjoy.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"Recently I have been on guard, watchful, or easily startled.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":true},{"question":"It has been hard finding motivation to do schoolwork, chores, or daily activities.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"It has been easy to lose my appetite and I have been eating less than usual.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"It has been difficult to enjoy daily activities or routines.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I have been feeling disconnected from friends, family, or colleagues.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I feel unwelcome and/or uncomfortable in social situations because of my culture or background.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I feel like I don't \"fit in.\" because my culture or background is different from others'.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I often feel the need to hide my culture or parts of my identity.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":1,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I have been experiencing moments of racing thoughts and restlessness that I find difficult to control.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":true},{"question":"I frequently worry about the future of various aspects of my life, such as work, relationships, or health.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I do not feel satisfied with my overall well-being.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I do not regularly spend time pursuing my hobbies and doing things I enjoy.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I find it hard to relax and wind down.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"My daily responsibilities, activities, or interactions feel overwhelming.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":true},{"question":"I sleep less than I normally do.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have too manny commitments (work, school, clubs, extracurriculars, etc.).","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have recently been experiencing nightmares or distressing dreams.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I often feel on edge or easily startled, even in non-threatening situations.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":1,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I have recently experienced bad major changes in my life and/or relationships.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":1,"Self-esteem":0,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":1,"user_response":false},{"question":"I am rarely congragulated or encouraged by my friends or family.","Depression":1,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I am not confident about how I look and how other people see me.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":1,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false},{"question":"I am very hesitant to try things and doubt my abilities.","Depression":0,"Anxiety":0,"Stress":0,"Self-esteem":1,"Cultural Sensitivity":0,"Quality of Life":0,"PTSD":0,"user_response":false}],"date":"Wed Feb 07 2024 02:56:28 GMT-0800 (Pacific Standard Time)"}]}}